Malta
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Malta
2.1.1.2.7
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1325
- Malta, 2.1.1.2.7
  - Grandmother, wearing black headdress, holding baby, circa 1918; 1; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Woman wearing headdress, circa 1918; 2; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Woman wearing headdress, holding baby, circa 1918; 3; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Woman wearing headdress, with two young boys, circa 1918; 4; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Lace worker sitting on bench, baby in carriage at left, circa 1918; 5; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Schneider and two women wearing headdresses, circa 1918; 6; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Schneider and two women wearing headdresses, circa 1918; 7; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Two officers with canes, standing on dock, circa 1918; 8; 4x5 (Box 1325)
  - Admiral Calthorpe, staff, American Consul Wilbur Keblinger and Lowell Thomas, circa 1918; 9; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Tent hospital, circa 1918; 10; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Street scene, circa 1918; 11; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Mouth of Grand Harbor, circa 1918; 12; 5x7 (Box 1325)
  - Girl and sheep in field, St. Paul’s Island in distance, circa 1918; 13; 5x7 (Box 1325)